I hate when puzzle pieces fall to the ground.
Indeed, you saw well.
Today we are going to do a puzzle. It's a very easy puzzle, I did it when I was little.
This here are the pieces, the pieces of the puzzle.
And I always start with the pieces that have a flat side.
Flat, those that are the edge of the puzzle.
Okay let's see, fire truck.
The fire truck is this, all this.
This is the bakery, well it's not a bakery, it's a café.
It's a piece, it's a head, inside a café.
This is from that café.
This is the café, see? Here the face of the man is missing. Now he has a face.
And here's the merry-go-round: there's a little boat, an elephant, and a fake fire truck -
and these are real.
And here is the wedding with the groom and the bride. The wedding.
I need this lady. Here's a lady with a purse.
I always remember that lady. See? This is the lady's face. The face.
Look ... how this is taking shape.
Here we have the man and the woman in the cafeteria.
The owner, the cook and here is a motorcyclist.
The fire trucks,
and here is the fire truck.
And here is the carousel and here I am missing the body of the lady. See? The body is missing.
By the way, what are firefighters for? What do firefighters do?
Leave it in a comment: What do firefighters do? What is your job?
The firefighters in this puzzle are not there just because, because they are beautiful. No.
They are here because they have work. Why do they have work? Because there is a fire,
there is a fire in a house.
Look! The body of the lady finally!
Have you seen that? Very satisfying.
You see It is already complete.
She's wearing heels, an oversized coat, and a purse.
And this looks like ... I don't know: chives? A leek? A leek.
This city seems very beautiful to me and has an air ...
an air that reminds me of a European city ...
That and the fact that the brand of the puzzle is called Ravensburger.
The puzzle reminds me of Bruges.
The streets of the historic center, the city center, the streets,
the road is made of pebbles.
What is the word...?
Mom! What is the stone floor of the city centers called?
Cobblestones
Cobblestones, that's it ... Today I don't know Spanish.
The floor of the streets is made of stones,
cobblestones and when the carriages pass with horses it sounds:
And that's because of the stone cobblestones.
It sounds, to sound a good word. So you can learn it. To sound.
It is a verb.
You can also say: this sounds familiar to me.
This is something that is familiar to you. Your face is familiar to me.
The fire ... Perfect.
It is a fire that has started in the distance, in a house in the countryside.
Far away from the city, far away. And it's on fire like Katniss Everdeen: book number two.
And all the firefighters are getting here.
They are going out of town, off the cobblestone streets,
to go out to put out the fire.
The only pieces I have are all green, from the field and rooftops.
See? They are all roofs: roof, roof, roof, roof and green the field.
It's the top.
Well I'm almost finished with the roofs at least.
There is a kitten on this roof.
Ok look, see how I'm doing.
I am very advanced. Have you seen? Here is the cathedral.
Good good good good good good good, this is done! It's done!
Ladies and gentlemen, this is done!
The last piece, let's put it together.
Ready ...
We have the fire trucks and the fire 'car', because this is not a truck, it is a car.
We have people pointing out the fire trucks
and the fire trucks are going to put out the fire on the outskirts of town.
Here is a merry-go-round and a kiosk.
There is a man buying a newspaper. One red traffic light and one green traffic light.
A policeman and ... our café.
This is a toy store here, you see? There are toys, a toy store.
This I think is a deli and this is meat.
And this is a shoe store, there are shoes.
And this here in blue is an awning.
And ... Here's the cathedral with some birds. There are many birds. Here are more birds.
Here is a child on a bicycle, a mother with the baby carriage
and here unfortunately there are missing pieces ...
But this is it, this is the puzzle.
Isn't it beautiful?
Have you learned any new vocabulary words? Has it been useful to you?
Do tell me.
The only thing left for you to do is subscribe and see you next week.
Bye!